[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Native American drink called Asi associated with in the Native American tradition?", "correct_answer": "Purification", "incorrect_answers": ["It was considered a panacea", "Warfare", "Power"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is one of the nicknames of the tiger shark?", "correct_answer": "Wastebasket of the Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Garbage Can of the Deep", "Predators  that will kill", "Killers of the Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fruit is believed to be the highest in vitamin C content?", "correct_answer": "Kakadu plum", "incorrect_answers": ["Lemon", "Kiwi", "Rose hip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In James Bonds Goldfinger, 007 knows the name of the villains plan, and this saves his life.  What was the name?", "correct_answer": "Operation Grand Slam", "incorrect_answers": ["Operation Barbarossa", "Operation Crossbow", "Operation Torch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Most of the land area of Tennessee is in the Eastern time zone.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Susan Sarandon won her first Academy Award for Best Actress for this 1995 drama movie.", "correct_answer": "Dead Man Walking", "incorrect_answers": ["Thelma  Louise", "The Client", "Lorenzos Oil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The kiss at the end of the wedding ceremony expresses a Christian belief and symbolizes the swapping of souls between the bride and the groom.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Xenophobia mean fear of  people you do not know?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bibliophobia means fear of reading the bible.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the restaurant that the friends frequent in the movie American Pie?", "correct_answer": "Dog Years", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Dog Jims", "Dog and Suds", "Doghouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2000 movie The Patriot, what was on the necklace that Benjamin gives Gabriels wife?", "correct_answer": "The North Star", "incorrect_answers": ["It was a locket with Gabriels face in it.", "Rust and dirt", "A gold and ruby heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A person who is afraid of heights, suffers from what disorder?", "correct_answer": "Acrophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Agoraphobia", "Arachnophobia", "Anglophobia"]}]